(Penny:)Oh, hey, if you guys
are free this weekend,
(Penny:)I won a night of
wine tasting from work.
(Leonard:)That sounds fun.
Mm-hmm.
(Leonard:)How come scientists don't win
free stuff like salespeople do?
'Cause we're not in it
for the stuff.
(Howard:)We're in it
for the groupies.
SHELDON:
Personally,
(Sheldon:)I find the notion of
external rewards demeaning.
(Sheldon:)I pursue science for the
intrinsic joy of discovery.
(Amy:)But you always say that
you want to win a Nobel Prize.
(Sheldon:)I also say don't contradict
me in front of my friends,
(Sheldon:)but that you
don't remember.
(Penny:)All right, well, let me know
if you guys want to go.
(Raj:)I would love to.
(Raj:)I do enjoy the complexity
of an aged Pinot noir.
(Leonard:)I'm sure that would pair nicely
(Leonard:)with your fried nuggets
of chicken.
(Amy:)Well, it sounds like
a nice night. We should go.
(Sheldon:)Wine again?
(Sheldon:)Yeah, no, thank you.
(Sheldon:)I like my grapes
the old-fashioned way:
(Sheldon:)in a juice box.
(Amy:)Well, I'm going.
(Amy:)You couldn't stop me from
getting a massage at the mall,
(Amy:)and you're not stopping me now.
(Sheldon:)I shouldn't have to
see my girlfriend
(Sheldon:)get groped in public
by another man.
(Amy:)And I shouldn't
have to see my boyfriend